Now listen, yo!
People put your guns up
First I'll run dat
Run around and shoot them
Brand new sound, yes still survival
Here comes the sound boy, live in this world
Intelligence, strength, and luck are swirling, flow
My swelled mind is candid
One punch to Banner in Savannah
An easy knockout, bam bam bam
One time for your mind, live through this
Around the world
It haunts me, the pain of the past
Around the noble god are borrowed things
When the seed that's sown flowers, whose is it
Live and fire the arrow of faith, more more more
There is no peace where you're going
Come on, stand up, don't give up the fight
Now, yes, this instant, die die die
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up, cut it open, break
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up, cut it open, break
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
The next 30 minutes will decide everything!
（加藤(かとう)）残り30分で全てが決まる
俺たちが帰れるか―
Either we get to go home,
or they win and we all die!
ヤツらが勝って
俺たちが全滅するか
どっちにしても
ここまで来たら やるしかない
Whatever happens, we've come
too far to turn back now.
Just Shoot Me!
For the moment, just think about staying alive!
（加藤）とにかく
生き残ることだけを考えよう
Come on!
行くぞ
Hey, Kei! Are you two dating?
（加藤）計(けい)ちゃん
その人と つきあってんのか？
Jeez, don't go saying things like that
in front of Kishimoto!
（計）
岸本(きしもと)の前で そういうこと言うなよ
How embarrassing!
恥ずかしいだろう
（聖(せい)）生きて帰れたら そのつもり
We plan to, if we can make it back alive.
（加藤）そうか
じゃ 生きて帰ってもらわないとな
Oh? You'll have to make sure
you make it back then!
We CAN get home, can't we?
We can all get home alive, right?
生きて帰れるのよね？
全員 家に帰れるんでしょう？
Kei was kind enough to kill the boss
for us this time...
今回は ボスを
計ちゃんが倒してくれたから―
あとは楽勝ッスよ
The rest will be a piece of cake!
Kei, I'm happy for you!
計ちゃん 良かったな
Cut it out already!
あのなぁ だから やめろって！
Hey, what's that?
おい あれ 何だ？
Where do you live again?
（トマオ）お前ん家(ち) どこだっけ？
（コンタ）西武(せいぶ)線 東長崎(ひがしながさき)
Higashi Nagasaki. It's on the Seibu line.
（トマオ）池袋(ブクロ)の近く？
（コンタ）そう
So it's close to Ikebukuro?
Yeah.
（北条(ほうじょう)）
お前 かわいい顔してんじゃん
You look pretty cute, you know that?
Let me see your face again.
もう１回 顔見せてみろよ
Jeez...
You mind if I stop by tomorrow?
（トマオ）
んじゃ あした 遊び行っていい？
Tomorrow?!
（コンタ）あしたかよ
Let's go!
いくぜ！
（トマオ・コンタ）うん？
Dammit!
（加藤）
ちくしょう… 一体 何のために
Why would someone do this?
It must've been those two guys, huh?
（計）あの２人組だな
どうして？ 仏像たちかもよ？
Why do you say that?
It could have been those statues.
（岸本）あいつらは
こんな殺し方は しないわ
Those things wouldn't have killed him like this.
Why...
一体…
Why did we even bother saving his life?
（加藤）何のために助けたんだ！
Kato...
加藤君…
俺たち 何のために…
What have we been doing this for?!
We're all trying to go back, together,
but now the priest is dead...
全員で帰ろうったって
坊さんは死んだし
あのミリタリーマニアも死んだ
Even that military nut is dead!
It's the same as last time,
and the time before that.
前回も その前も そうだった
それに
俺 難しいこと よく分かんねえけど
I don't really understand all these
complicated things...
こんなのって ありなのかよ？
But why did THIS have to happen?!
ホームレスだからって
殺していいのかよ？
How can it be okay to kill someone
just because he's homeless?!
俺たちが帰ろうとしてるのは
どういう世界なんだよ？
What kind of a world are we
trying to get back to?!
We've suffered for it... Bled for it...
こんなに苦労して血ぃ流して
俺たちは どこに帰ろうってんだ？
But what the hell kind of place
are we trying to return to?!
線路に落ちたホームレスを
誰も助けようとしない世界へか？
A world where no one will help a homeless man
who's fallen on the train tracks?
A world where a homeless man who
never did anything to anyone
何もしていないホームレスが
頭かち割られる世界へか？
gets his head smashed open?!
Kato!
（計）加藤！
（加藤）ハッ…
You told me before...
お前 前に言ってたよな？
“いちばん帰りたいのは俺だ”って
You want to go home more than any of us.
（計）
だったら 帰るしかねえだろう
If that's true, then going back
is your only option, right?
みんな同じなんだよ　誰だって
The same goes for the rest of us... ALL of us.
Huh? What's wrong with me?
あれ？ 変だな
Up until a minute ago, I thought
this was where I belonged.
俺 さっきまで―
ここが俺の居場所だなんて
思ってなかったか？
I get it.
そっか　俺…
I... I really do want to go home.
ホントは帰りたいんだ
まだ死にたくないんだ
I don't want to die just yet.
Kurono?
玄野(くろの)君？
Yeah...
Let's get going!
行こうぜ　時間がねえ
We don't have much time!
That's right!
（加藤）そうだな！
You don't mind if I take him, do you?
（聖）
私 もらっていいのね？ あの子
（岸本）
えっ？ “もらって”だなんて…
Huh? "Take him"?
（聖）じゃ いいのね？
Good, so you don't mind.
No. Kurono seems too different, so...
（岸本）玄野君は違うみたいだから
（聖）何が？
Different how?
Like he and I... are on different levels.
次元が　私とは
Hey, hey, hey!
（トマオ）おいおいおい…
いっぱい いんじゃねえかよ
There's a whole bunch of 'em in here!
They're not moving, though.
（コンタ）動かねえぞ
But are they gonna START moving again?
（トマオ）
また こいつら動くのかよ？
おい リーダー どうすんだ？
Hey, leader! What do we do now?
（北条）待て　こいつで見てみる
Hold on. I'll examine them with this.
骨とか内臓とかあったら
今のうちに攻撃するぞ
If I see bones or organs,
we'd better attack while we can.
Can we really beat them
without the others here?
俺らだけで勝てんのかよ？
Hey, compared to that huge one,
this should be a piece of cake.
あのでっかいのに比べたら
楽勝だろう
（千手観音）
いつぬるさらせに よくらせよ
Tsunurusaraseniyokuraseyo
Nikaresamijikisugeyo
（千手観音）にかれさみじきすげよ
Shinimosusesamu
（仏像星人）しにもすさせむ
（千手観音）きゃすらはもからぬ
Kyasurahamokarane
Shinimosusesamu
Hanushinusuru
むげにもうごろむ
Mugenimougoromu
Hanushinusuru
（仏像星人）
うらはいぬふどしるずず
Mugenimougoromu
Korahainufudoshiruzuzu
I guess there's no need to examine them.
見てみるまでも なさそうだな
That looks like the fast statue from before!
さっきの速いヤツに似てる！
取り囲め！
Surround it!
Kunuyunumunutsuchiukunushimusunu
Kutsugusenuro-to
Kuyutsuruorugukurusuorugukurusu
So we're going to fight all of them?
やっぱ こいつら全部と やんのか？
What now? What do we do, leader?
（トマオ）どうする？
どうすんだよ？ リーダー
Stay back.
後ろに…
スーツ着てないヤツは後ろに下がれ
If you're not wearing a suit, just stay back.
Well well! Here comes a challenger!
（コンタ）
オオッ… チャレンジャー登場！
（北条）あ… 危ねえぞ　やめとけ
Hey, that's dangerous! Cut it out!
Umuyukurusumusumunukurusuyuruu
（仏像星人）
うむゆくるすむすむぬくるすゆるう
I said cut it out!
（北条）おい やめとけって！
He's already killed a bunch of
those things with his bare hands.
（トマオ）
あいつ 素手で何匹も殺してたし
大丈夫じゃねえの？
I think he'll be okay.
（コンタ）いやぁ どうかねえ？
Hmm, I don't know about that...
（ＪＪ）テーイッ！
（受け止める音）
（仏像星人）フッ…
うむゆろむゆ ふひゅひゅひゅ
Umuyuromuyu Fu-hyuhyuhyu
テイッ！
（受け止める音）
ワッツ？
What?!
（トマオ・コンタ）あっ…
（北条）逃げろ！ あとは俺が…
Get outta here! Leave this to me. This is bad...
やべえぞ！ あいつ 強(つえ)え
Those things are strong!
Whoa!
（コンタ）オオッ！
（トマオ）すげえ！
Damn!
Sumunukuyukkurusutekurumu
（仏像星人）
すむぬくゆ くるすてくるむ
（コンタ）ウワーッ！
Oh, shit!
（トマオ）やべえ！
You're not wearing a suit so GET OUTTA HERE!
（北条）
スーツ着てないヤツは逃げろ！
Whoa, whoa, WHOA!
（コンタ）おいおいおい…
（トマオ）ちょ… ちょ… ちょっと
What's going on?
Just run! RUN!
とにかく逃げろ！ 逃げろー！
It's not good! This thing's too fast!
I can't catch up to it!
（岸本）
ダメ！ 速すぎる！ 追いつけない！
ンッ… 止めたぞ！ 今だ！
I got him! Do it now!
（加藤）ウワッ！
Kato!
（計）加藤！
（破裂音）
（加藤）ウワーッ… アッ…
（加藤）ウッ…
（岸本）加藤君！
Kato!
The transfer... It hasn't started yet.
（加藤）
転送は？ まだ始まらないのか？
Aren't they done over there?
向こうは まだ終わってないのか？
あと何分あるんだ？
How much time do we have left?
（トマオ）どうするよ？
こいつら かなり やべえぞ
What are we gonna do? These things
are frickin' deadly!
（コンタ）出口 塞いでんだ！
逃がさねえ気だぞ！
And they're blocking the exit!
They're not gonna let us get away!
You guys don't have suits on,
so stay behind me.
（北条）
スーツ着てないヤツは 俺の後ろに
Sadako, you back me up.
サダコ 俺をサポートしろ！
I don't care who, but one of you
has to get out of here and get help.
どっちでもいい　こっから出て
助けを呼んできてくれ
Hey, how about now?
おい 今…
（コンタ）うん？
１…
（コンタ）あっ…
One...
（トマオ）２の… ３！
Two...
Three!
Listen... we'll manage on our own somehow.
いいか？ こいつら
俺らだけで なんとかすんだぞ
（貞代(さだよ)）うん…
あっ… しま…
Shit.
We look pretty lame, huh?
俺たち カッコ悪いな
（トマオ）逃げてばっかだもんな
Yeah. We're always running away!
Hey, you guys!
（コンタ）お～い！ あっちで…
（トマオ）いっぱい いるぞ！
（加藤）１体じゃないのか？
There's a bunch of them!
Not just one?
（コンタ）５匹は いたぜ
There were five of them for sure!
That creepy girl and the good-looking
guy are taking them on alone!
（トマオ）気持ち悪い女と
男前の にいちゃんが―
２人で相手してる
サダコ… ハァハァ… 大丈夫か？
Sadako!
Are you alright?
Run...
逃げろ… 逃げろ サダコ
Run, Sadako!
Um... Your book arrives next week, right?
（岸本）
あの… 来週 届くんでしたよね？
Huh?
Miranda Foster's Labyrinth.
（岸本）
ミランダ・フォスターの「迷宮」
（聖）どうして知ってるの？
How did you know about that?
この間 私 あのお店にいて
I was in the store the other day.
You were in THAT bookstore?
あの本屋さんに？
What kind of book is it?
どういう本なんですか？
Well, I still haven't read it...
ああ… まだ読んでないから
Oh. Yeah.
（岸本）あっ そうですよね
（聖）でも“迷宮”って
ちょっと やんなっちゃう感じよね
But I get the feeling I'm not going
to like Labyrinth very much.
えっ？
（聖）今の私たち―
Right now it feels like we're IN a labyrinth.
迷宮に入り込んだみたいだもん
（岸本）ああ…
Oh.
They say there's no labyrinth
you can't get out of, but...
出られない迷宮はないって説も
あったりするけどね
いくぞ！
Let's do it!
お… おい…
Hey.
This is bullshit.
（北条）くだらねえよ
何もかも くだらねえよ
All of it... it's just bullshit.
We dropped our suits and guns, huh?
（トマオ）スーツと銃
落としちまったんだよな
You wanna go look for them?
捜すか
（トマオ）ああ
Yeah.
It's a temple, so you might as well
say "Namu Amida butsu!":)
イヤーッ！
（計）ハッ…
Kishimoto!
岸本！ 岸本！
KISHIMOTO!
アア…
（計）何も見るな！
Don't look at it!
騒いでパニクったら帰れなくなるぞ
岸本 落ち着け！
If you lose control and start panicking,
you'll never make it back!
Pull yourself together, Kishimoto!
玄野君…
Kurono...
We can go back! We can do it!
俺たちは帰れる　帰れるんだ！
必ず帰るんだ！
We're all going back no matter what!
We're going back.
（加藤）帰るんだ…
We ARE going home.
帰るんだ みんなで…
みんなで帰るんだ
All of us... we're all going home together.
Okay!
よし！
ウオーッ！
（計）加藤！
Kato!
やった！ あっ…
He did it!
（岸本）ンッ！
（計）岸本！
Kishimoto!
Protect Kato!
加藤君を！
（計）えっ？
Protect Kato... Please!
加藤君をお願い！
（岸本）
ああ… なんか 気持ちいいかも
This... feels good for some reason.
I used to be happy when people would
tell me, "You're such a good girl."
“あなたは
ホントに いい子ね”って―
言われるのが うれしくて
幼稚園ぐらいまで
それ すごく うれしくて…
It made me happy up until about kindergarten.
でも だんだん
うれしくなくなってきちゃって
But then, even if people praised me for
something, it made me less and less satisfied.
褒められても
Kurono! This feels so good!
玄野君 これ すっごく気持ちいいよ
When I'm with Kato... When I hold him like this...
加藤君といると…
こうしてると とっても暖(あった)かくて
優しくて ホッとできて…
He feels warm and gentle. I feel so relaxed.
We've had to face a lot of difficulties recently...
ちょっと前まで
つらいこと多かったけど―
But as long as I'm with Kato,
everything will be fine.
加藤君といれば大丈夫かも
This is enough. If something like this
can feel so good, it's all I need.
もう いい
これだけ気持ちよければ もう…
Kurono...
玄野君…
I'm sorry, but I want to spend my
last moments with Kato.
（岸本）ごめん
でも 最期は加藤君と一緒がいい
出られない迷宮はないんだって
お願い 加藤君を…
They say there's no labyrinth
you can't get out of...
Please, take care of Kato.
Please, Kei!
お願い 計ちゃん！
How long do you plan on studying?!
（岸本の母親）
いつまで やってんの？
は～い
All right, all right.
Kato...
加藤君 好き…
I love you.
Kishimoto...
岸本…
This can't be...
こんなのって…
こんなのって！
This can't be happening!
Shit!
くそ… ウワッ！
イヤーッ！
NO!
岸本…
Kishi...
Kishimo...
Kishimoto...
Kishi...
きしも…
Kishimo...
負けねえ　俺は 負け…
I won't be beaten... I won't...
Are you going to kill all of us?
（聖）私たちを全員 殺すつもり？
What should I do? Leader!
どうすればいいの？ リーダー！
I don't have a chance against this thing!
こいつ 私じゃ勝てそうもない
Leader! You're not dead yet!
リーダー！
まだ死んでないんでしょう？
Look what they've done to Kei!
計君が やられちゃったんだよ！
Is he dead?
死んだのか？
死んだのか？ 計ちゃんが
Is Kei dead?!
No, he's not dead yet! But at this rate...
死んでない！
死んでないけど このままじゃ…
We still have a chance!
（加藤）まだ なんとかなる！
いったん外に出よう！
For now, we should just get out of here!
Can you carry him? Can you carry Kei?!
連れ出せるか？ 計ちゃんを
All right, I'll try!
分かった　やってみる！
Stay alive... Kei.
（聖）生きて
計君
You're going for a drive with me!
私とドライブすんだから
Hang in there!
頑張って生きて！
Stay alive!
We're not going to die that easily!
そう簡単には死なないわよ 私たち
Let's go!
（加藤）外へ出るぞ！
Ka...
加藤…
Kato...
うん？ どうした？ 計ちゃん
What is it? Kei!
I want you to...
俺を…
Kill me.
殺してくれ
あっ…
（聖）何言ってるの？
What are you talking about?!
Kill me... please.
（計）殺してくれ…
I'm not going to make it.
もうダメだ
I know I'm going to die.
俺 死ぬって…
Kato...
加藤… 俺を撃て
Shoot me.
Kato...
（計）加藤…
Just shoot me!
俺を撃てっ！
We all start out as pure and innocent babes
Even if you taste the bitter fruit,
don't be discouraged, walk straight
I know it's in the past, but the rain still stings
I'm lonely as floating ice
I kiss your thin finger
And remember you crying
Even if this is the end
I won't forget your last kiss
I won't forget
I won't forget his kiss
Screams.
（加藤）悲鳴 流血 嫉妬
Blood.
Jealousy.
Sighs.
ため息 希望…
Hope...
そして 神さま 願わくば…
and God.
I hope.
Next episode: Big Brother?
次回 “兄ちゃん？”